{
    "subject": "resource/Licence_to_Kill",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Films_produced_by_Albert_R._Broccoli",
    "human_readable": "Licence to Kill is the subject of the category Films produced by Albert R. Broccoli.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9404117465019226,
            "question": "What is the subject of the category 'Films produced by Albert R. Broccoli'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7990735173225403,
            "question": "Is 'Licence to Kill' a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7713629603385925,
            "question": "Who was responsible for producing the film 'Licence to Kill'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7636396884918213,
            "question": "What other categories of film productions might Albert R. Broccoli have been involved with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7466917037963867,
            "question": "What other films might Albert R. Broccoli have produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6763396263122559,
            "question": "How many films has Albert R. Broccoli produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5302033424377441,
            "question": "Name a famous film series that Albert R. Broccoli was involved with."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48362576961517334,
            "question": "What genre is 'Licence to Kill' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.471376895904541,
            "question": "When might 'Licence to Kill' have been released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45999279618263245,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors associated with 'Licence to Kill'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Licence to Kill is the subject of the category Films produced by Albert R. Broccoli.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6363_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When might 'Licence to Kill' have been released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6363_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is 'Licence to Kill' likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6363_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a famous film series that Albert R. Broccoli was involved with.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6363_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6363_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6363_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6363_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6363_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6363_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6363_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6363_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6363_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6363_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6363_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to try another query!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nExplanation: The documents do not mention that Licence to Kill was a film produced by Albert R. Broccoli. In fact, one of the documents mentions that Albert R. Broccoli has openly stated that he disliked the handling of the marketing and promotion for Licence to Kill, but it does not suggest that he produced the film."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents mention that Albert R. Broccoli was involved in producing the film Licence to Kill, which supports the statement that the film falls under the category of \"Films produced by Albert R. Broccoli.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Albert R. Broccoli was involved in the production of Licence to Kill as a producer, but the film is not an example of films produced by him, rather it is one of the films that were produced before his death in 1996 and features actors/crew members who worked with him during their active time.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}